{
 "data": [
    {
      "question": "Jamaica is an island in ______ Caribbean.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Every year Brian goes to ______ South America and spends a month in Peru.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Normally, before the Muhalla, Villages, City, State, and Country;",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The biggest freshwater lake in the world is ______ Lake Baikal in Russia. It's 400 miles long and 80 miles wide.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Normally, before the Muhalla, Villages, City, State, and Country; ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "There were lots of fish in _______ lake and we caught several big ones.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n - The: used when you are about to make it clear which person or thing you mean",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The biggest ocean in the world is ______ Pacific . It covers 32.6% of the world's surface.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We were very pleased when our friends ______ Hendersons became our neighbours.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n-Normally, Proper Noun doesn't take any ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Norway is in ______ northern Europe.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- In the north of \n- In northern....",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Not many people know that ______ Gobi desert has mountains and forests, as well as sand.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The most famous city in Morocco is perhaps ______ Casablanca .",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Normally, before the Muhalla, Villages, City, State, and Country;",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Japan, Thailand and Malaysia are countries in ______ Far East .",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- The Far East",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "12",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ] 
}